myvouchercodes.co.uk 2018-09-09

# Privacy Policy - MyVoucherCodes.co.uk

## 1\. Who we are and how to contact us

We are The Global Voucher Group Limited, the owner and operator of [www.myvouchercodes.co.uk](https://www.myvouchercodes.co.uk/). The Global Voucher Group Limited (referred to as “we”, “us” and “our” in this privacy policy) is the controller responsible for personal information processed by it.

It is important that you read this privacy policy carefully so that you are fully aware of how and why we use your personal information. We do not knowingly collect personal information relating to children under the age of 16 and children under the age of 16 should not use this website. 

We have appointed a data protection officer (DPO) to oversee our data protection and privacy practices. If you have any questions about this privacy policy or if you wish to exercise your legal rights set out in this privacy policy, please contact our DPO using the details below. 

_Contact details_

**Our contact details are:**

The Global Voucher Group Limited  
Medius House  
2 Sheraton Street  
London  
W1F 8BH

Email: [support@myvouchercodes.co.uk](mailto:support@myvouchercodes.co.uk)

**Our DPO’s contact details are:**

Email: [dpo@myvouchercodes.co.uk](mailto:dpo@myvouchercodes.co.uk)

## 2\. Changes to this privacy policy

We reserve the right to amend or modify this privacy policy from time to time. All amended versions of this privacy policy will be posted on our website. 

## 3\. What types of personal information we collect

Depending upon the way in which you use our website and the individual products and services you are looking to buy, we may obtain the following: 

  1. personal information so that we can identify who you are. For example, this information may include your name and date of birth; 
  2. personal information so that we can contact you. For example, this information may include your home address, your email address and your contact telephone numbers;
  3. behavioural and/or technical personal information. For example, this information may include details about how you browse our website and the devices and technology you use to browse our website. 

## 4\. How we use personal information, the lawful grounds upon which we rely and why

**How might you use my personal information?** | **What lawful basis will you have to use my personal information in this way?** | **Why do you use my personal information in this way?**  
---|---|---  
We may process your personal information in order to send you service communications. | This processing of your personal information is **necessary** so that we can provide our services to you in accordance with our website terms and conditions. | Without processing your personal information in this way, we would be unable to provide our services to you.  
If you opt-in to receive marketing from us, we may process your personal information for the purposes of providing our marketing to you. For example, if you opt-in to receive our marketing, we may send you newsletters, information about our latest offers, products and promotions and more. | We will only process your personal information for the purposes of providing offers, reminders and promotional information to you with your **consent**. | All of our marketing is carefully drafted and intended always to be topical, relevant and useful for our customers.  
If you choose to take part in any of our competitions, prize draws or promotions, we may process your personal information for the purposes of administering the competition, prize draw or promotion and for the purposes of contacting you in the event that you are a prize winner. | We will only process your personal information in connection with our competitions, prize draws or promotions with your **consent**. | Without processing your personal information in this way, we would be unable to provide any competition, prize draw or promotion which you may choose to take part in.  
We may process your personal information in order to personalise or improve aspects of our service delivery and for troubleshooting and other quality control and testing purposes, including for the purposes of responding to any queries or complaints about our services raised by you or our approved partners and third party and product providers. | We have a **legitimate interest** in processing your personal information in order to ensure that we are always able to provide an excellent quality of service. | It is in our legitimate interests to process your personal information in this way so that we can provide an excellent quality of service. To do this, we regularly monitor and seek to improve our interactions with you and our approved partners and third-party product providers. This helps us to understand how we can better satisfy your needs and hence grow our business. Sometimes we may also need to access your personal information in order to resolve any queries or complaints which are made about our service. Our work in this area ensures that we can continue to provide the level of service which you have rightly come to expect from us.  
We may process your personal information in order to comply with any and all legal and/or regulatory obligations to which we are subject. | This processing of your personal information is **necessary** so that we can comply with **legal obligations** to which we are subject. | We are subject to numerous laws, rules and requirements. Sometimes it is necessary for us to process your personal information in order to obey the laws, rules and requirements to which we are subject.  
  
## 5\. How we collect personal information

We collect personal information from you when you interact or engage with our website including when you register an account with us. We may also collect personal information from you when you talk to us on the phone, by post or online including via email, social media and mobile device apps. We may also engage with you and hence collect personal information from you if you choose to provide feedback or take part in any of our other market research initiatives, customer surveys or competitions, prize draws or promotions. 

## 6\. Third parties with whom we may exchange personal information

We may share personal information with or receive personal information from: 

  1. other members of our corporate group; 
  2. law enforcement agencies and regulatory bodies, including the Information Commissioner’s Office; 
  3. third parties to whom we may sell, transfer or merge parts of our business or assets or third parties whose business or assets we may acquire. 

## 7\. Sending personal information outside the European Economic Area (EEA)

We will only ever send personal information to providers outside the EEA if those providers are required to protect personal information in exactly the same way they would be required to protect personal information if they were based within the EEA. This means that we will only send personal information to a non-EEA country if: 

  1. the European Commission has determined that the relevant non-EEA country affords an adequate level of protection for personal information; 
  2. pursuant to an agreement between us and the relevant provider based in the non-EEA country which contains data protection clauses adopted or approved by the European Commission; or
  3. we send data to the US pursuant to the Privacy Shield. 

## 8\. How long we retain personal information

We keep personal information which is provided to us only for as long as is reasonably necessary thereafter in order to: 

  1. respond fully to any questions or complaints; 
  2. evidence that we have treated customers fairly or satisfy some other legal, accounting, tax or reporting requirement; and
  3. establish, exercise or defend legal claims in accordance with statutory limitation periods. 

## 9\. Data security

The security of personal information is extremely important to us and hence we have put in place appropriate security measures to protect personal information from being accidentally lost, used or accessed in an unauthorised way. 

## 10\. Your legal rights

  1. _Right of access_

You have a right to know whether we are processing your personal information. If we are processing your personal information, you also have a right to request copies of your personal information that we are processing and certain further information, including the purposes of our processing and the recipients or categories of recipients to whom we have disclosed (or will disclose) your personal information. 

  2. _Right to rectification_

You have the right to require us to rectify or complete any inaccurate or incomplete personal information that we are holding about you. 

  3. _Right to erasure_

You have a right to ask us to erase your personal information. This is also known as the “right to be forgotten”. We must erase your personal information following your request except in limited circumstances prescribed by law, such as where we need to retain your personal information in order to comply with a legal obligation or in order to establish, exercise or defend legal claims. In these circumstances, we will restrict our processing of your personal information by putting it “beyond use”. This means that your personal information is deleted from our website and retained only in a separate and restricted database, where it will not be processed for any purpose other than as detailed above. Access to this database is managed by our DPO and is strictly limited. 

  4. _Right to restriction of processing_

You have a right to require us to restrict processing of your personal information where: -

    1. you believe that the personal information we hold about you is inaccurate and we require reasonable time to verify the accuracy of that personal information; 
    2. your personal information has been unlawfully processed by us but you do not want us to erase that personal information; 
    3. it is no longer necessary for us to keep your personal information for the purposes for which they were collected by us but they are required by you for the establishment, exercise or defence of legal claims; or
    4. you exercise your right to object to processing and we require reasonable time to verify whether there are any overriding grounds upon which we may rely in order to continue that processing.

  5. _Right to data portability_

If we process your personal information with your consent or because it is necessary for us to do so in order to provide our service to you, you may require us to move, copy or transfer that personal information to you or another third party in a structured, commonly used and machine-readable format.

  6. _Right to object_

You have a right to object to our processing of your personal information where we are processing that personal information on legitimate interest grounds. We will stop processing this personal information if you exercise your right to object unless there are overriding grounds upon which we may rely in order to continue that processing or unless that processing is necessary in order to establish, exercise or defend legal claims.

You also have a right to object to our processing of your personal information for direct marketing purposes. We will stop processing your personal information for direct marketing purposes if you request us to do so.

  7. _Right to withdraw consent_

If we process your personal information with your consent, you have a right to withdraw your consent at any time. If you withdraw your consent, we may be unable to continue to provide certain services to you but we will inform you if that is the case.

## 11\. Cookies

For information on the cookies we use, please click here: <https://www.myvouchercodes.co.uk/cookies>

## 12\. Third Party Websites

When you leave our website, you are also strongly encouraged to read the privacy policy of every website that you visit in order to satisfy yourself as to the purposes for which those third-party website owners and operators will use any personal information you give to them.

## 13\. Complaints

You can complain to us or the Information Commissioner’s Office at any time. However, we appreciate the chance to deal with your concerns so please do contact us in the first instance.
